[Music] I'm
[Música]
going to fire Paula I can
voy a despedirlo a paula pueda
fire him my channel smells like dog when you
despedirlo mi canal huela perro cuando
enter a house that they don't clean much
entréis en una casa que no limpian mucho
and it smells like dog the machine hits you it was
y huela perro la maquinita te pega
swarming offered it knows with my channel
pululaba ofertada sabe con mi canal
fly dog ​​my
vuela perro
channel fly dog ​​I
mi canal vuela perro literalmente me
'm literally getting ready halfway through I already put the
estoy preparando a la mitad ya ponía la
intro the next excerpt ok and I
intro el siguiente extracto vale y me
see that this clown Paula puts me
veo que me pone el payaso este de paula
on the front page ok first frame that I
en primera portada vale primer frame que
find with a gesture ok the title of the
me encuentro de gesto vale el título del
excerpt blond explodes against the
extracto rubio explota contra el
minister of bread of Spain ok the
ministro de pan de españita vale el
minister the minister of what minister
ministro el ministro de que ministro
haim a good minister we have too many here
haim un bueno ministro nos sobran aquí
in Spain ok in fact and now it says
en españa vale de hecho y ahora pone
below the churra of infinity
abajo el churra del infinito
and I'm there behind I'm already shooting thank you very much
y estoy ahí atrás ya tiro yo muchísimas
welcome and I'm there with with
gracias bienvenido y estoy yo ahí con
with the gauntlet of tanos with all
con con el guantelete de tanos con todos
my channels no but of course I have 6
mis canales no pero claro tengo 6
channels the 6 gems are not there okay
canales no están ahí las 6 gemas vale
javi oliveira hub the wimp javi the
javi oliveira hub el canijo javi el
wimp to javi the canine
canijo a javi el canino
these are the things that I have to
estas son las cosas que tengo que
put up with because of because of my
aguantar por culpa de por culpa de mi
gamer equipment cube thank you very much king
equipo gamer cubo muchas gracias rey
let's see what  has crossed the Rubicon, little
vamos a ver qué le ha pasado el rubicón
Spain, blond, blond, he seems to be coming on
españita rubio rubio se ve se viene muy
top, he seems to be coming on top since, since he
arriba se ve muy arriba desde que desde
's not in Spain, since the Treasury doesn't keep an
que no está en españa desde que hacienda
eye on him, yapo, caro, he's coming on
no le vigila yapo caro ya se viene muy
top now and he dares to say
arriba y se atreve a decir cualquier
anything, no,
cosa no
wow, I
guau
can't say it, the dogs say it
no puedo decir lo dice los perros
too, well, let's see the video,
también bueno a ver vamos a ver el vídeo
how disgusting to drink this, he's blond, and he
qué asco de beber esto que es rubio y le
responded to the minister like this.
respondió a el ministro de esta manera
This photo the blond has posted now on
esta foto tiene el rubio puesta ahora en
Twitter, damn, those times when I
twitter [__] que tiempos en los que yo
was on Twitter, don't you hear, why don't we
estaba en twitter no oye porque no
do something to organize, demand that
hacemos algo para organizar reclamar a
Twitter let me come back
twitter que me deje volver
on Twitter, let Javi come back, well,
por twitter deja volver a javi bueno
well,
bueno
Alfonso Muñoz Cuenca, I don't know who he is, I'm going to
alfonso muñoz cuenca no sé quién es voy
look at him, see, look at him, literally, well,
a mirarlo ver mirarlo literalmente bueno
Alexa,
alexa
not talking, Alexa, I bet she
oye alexa no habla
had a loose cable, Alexa,
alexa a que tenía un cable suelto alexa
good afternoon,
buenas tardes
Alexa,
alexa
Alexa, Alexa,
álex a alexa
but Alomar, something is restarting, it's not
pero alomar se está reiniciando algo no
there, it's not going to arrive,
esta es que no se va a llegar
but its light is turning on,
pero está dando vuelta su luz
Alexa,
alexa
what do I do with Alexa,
qué hago con alexa
are you connected to the Wi-Fi? Talk but it's
está conectados al wifi hable pero tanto
taking so long, it's taking so
tarda
long.
tanto tarda
Well,
bueno
go at your own pace, but I need to know
que vaya a su ritmo pero necesito saber
who  was this minister well I'm going to read
quién era este ministro bueno voy a leer
on twitter while you see if between
en twitter mientras ves a ver si entre
those it connects the same thing that takes a long
eso se conecta lo propio que tarda mucho
[ __ ] it's a wifi
[__] es un wifi
not for nothing but that a minister
no es por nada pero que un ministro
in parentheses only 27 thousand followers
entre paréntesis sólo 27 mil seguidores
talking about pensions have 33
hablando sobre pensiones tengan 33 me
likes and rubios 17 million saying that he's
gustas y rubios 17 millones diciendo que
going to bet have ten thousand
se va a apostar tenga diez mil
three hundred
trescientos
pau the truth is I'm going to fire you man if you
pau la verdad voy a despedirte tío si me
put this ceiling on me and you cover the minister's tweet I do
pones este techo y me tapas el tuit del
n't know what with the logo put to javi
no sé qué con el logo puesto a javi
I'm sick of dog memes
estoy harto de los memes de perros
also the churra wow face smiling with his
además el churra guau cara sonriendo con
eyes closed that's why we love you
los ojos cerrados por eso te queremos
abi ha ha ha ha ha what a hypocrite the [ __ ]
abi ja ja ja ja ja qué hipócrita el [__]
jabil canijo if you take him and oliveira the
jabil canijo si lo coges y oliveira la
xunta and not see basically the minister
xunta y no ver básicamente el ministro
what he is complaining and he is
lo que se está quejando y está
whining okay he has less
lloriqueando vale que él tiene menos
followers than rubios and the things
seguidores que el rubios y que las cosas
that he puts have less likes that the
que él ponga tiene menos me gusta que el
ruble
rublo
puts the ruby ​​maybe the
le pone el rubí a lo mejor el señor
minister should pass the godó ward in
ministro debería pasarse el godó ward en
god of war difficulty until 7
dificultad dios de la guerra hasta las 7
m to have that online
m para tener eso online
ah no, only I can do that haha ​​hey hey, really good, really good, oh god, the political class we have Alexa, who is Alfonso Muñoz Cuenca? Here's something I found on the web and I translated according to wikipedia.org. Alfonso Muñoz, born in
wikipedia.org alfonso muñoz nacido en
1932, is a Colombian sprinter. Hey,
1932 es un velocista colombiano
really, these girls are no good to us
oye de verdad esta estas chicas no nos
Karime
karime
I think she's confused with the trip
yo creo que es aturdido con el viaje
Alexa, let's say the exam doesn't work, it
alexa sea el examen no da una
seems like a collaborator of 'sálvame'
parece un colaborador de 'sálvame' se
makes up the information and goes to
inventa la información y a tomar por
hell
culo
Alexa has me worried.
alexa me tiene preocupado
Sorry, I haven't been able to find the
perdona no he podido encontrar la
answer to what you asked me Alexa, I have
respuesta a lo que me has preguntado
n't asked you anything, thanks
alexa no te he preguntado nada gracias
for informing me
por informarme
Alexa, she's messing with me, I
alexa me está vacilando
never have bad intentions, much
jamás tengo malas intenciones y mucho
less do I want to laugh at you
menos quiero reírme de ti
Alexa, in love mode.
alexa modo enamorada
Hi, if you prove that you are
hola si demuestras que eres lo
enough of an expert in love, you will be able to
suficientemente experto en amor podrás
unlock my in love mode. You will only
desbloquear mi modo enamorada sólo
have to guess the author of at
tendrás que adivinar el autor de al
least two of the four phrases that I
menos dos de las cuatro frases que te
will tell you, okay, let's start,
diré vale empezamos
here is a phrase related to
aquí tienes una frase relacionada con
romantic expectations or whatever.  whether
las expectativas amorosas o lo que sea
you're looking it's not going to come the
que estés buscando no va a llegar en la
way you expect who said it
manera en que lo esperas quién lo dijo
the writer haruki murakami or the
el escritor haruki murakami o el
singer malú ma i
cantante malú ma
think that evidently maluma
yo creo que evidentemente maluma
goes so far it wasn't easy this
vaya hasta allá do no era fácil esta
phrase was included by the famous writer
frase la incluyó el famoso escritor
murakami in his novel taza en la orilla
murakami en su novela taza en la orilla
here you have a unique love phrase
aquí tienes una frase de amor única
i'm trembling to think that i already
estoy temblando de pensar que ya te
have you here by my side and i promise not to
tengo aquí a mi lado y prometo no
let go of your hand who said it
soltarte de la mano quien la dijo
antonio orozco in one of his songs or
antonio orozco en una de sus canciones o
demi moore in the movie ghost
demi moore en la película ghost
antonio loco
antonio loco
brabo you got it right few songs
brabo has acertado pocas canciones le
sing so beautifully about the first
cantan tan bonito a los primeros
moments of love like the song
instantes del amor como el tema
temblando by orozco
temblando de orozco
here you have a phrase related to
aquí tienes una frase relacionada con el
love you have to learn to get up from
amor tienes que aprender a levantarte de
the table when love is no longer being served who
la mesa cuando ya no se sirve amor quién
said it the presenter carlos sobera with
lo dijo el presentador carlos sobera con
the singer nina simone
la cantante nina simone
the presenter carlos sobera
el presentador carlos sobera
wow you have not been lucky incredible
vaya no has tenido suerte increíble
here you have an essential love phrase
aquí tienes una frase de amor
for the absence of
imprescindible por la ausencia de la
life there is no life without love who left it
vida no hay vida sin amor quien la dejó
was the poet rosalía de castro with the
fue el poetisa rosalía de castro con la
singer malú
cantante malú
evidently  it was bad
evidentemente fue malo
you have failed is a phrase from the poem you
has fallado es una frase del poema tu
for me I for you good mine by the great
para mi yo para ti bien mío de la gran
'rosalia de castro'
'rosalía de castro'
this has been all and I'm sorry to tell you that you
esto ha sido todo y siento decirte que
don't know enough about love to
no sabes tanto de amor como para
unlock my in love mode I have
desbloquear mi modo enamorada tengo
many more love phrases for you to keep
muchas más frases de amor para que sigas
playing do you want to try again
jugando quieres volver a intentarlo en
another time sorry that was a yes or a
otro momento disculpa eso fue un sí o un
no
no
sorry that was a yes no I
disculpa eso fue un sí no
agree thanks for participating
de acuerdo gracias por participar
someday I will manage to win
lograré algún día conquistar el corazón
Alexa's heart well
de alexa bueno
and let's continue watching the video
y vamos a seguir viendo el vídeo
the spokesperson for social inclusion of the
el portavoz inclusión social de la
twitter account of the man
cuenta de twitter de del hombre
a new impulse spokesperson for inclusion and
un nuevo impulso portavoz de inclusión y
social security in the senate to hear he
seguridad social en el senado para oír
is envious that he doesn't have many
tiene envidia de que no tiene muchos
followers he has a
seguidores
thousand followers
tiene mil seguidores
schalke has 27 thousand followers in other words he is not a
schalke tiene 27 mil seguidores o sea no
minister he is
es un ministro
a minister the man this alfonso
es un ministro el hombre este alfonso
muñoz who is not a new minister as such
muñoz que no es nuevo ministro como tal
what he is complaining about is not that
de lo que se está quejando no es de que
he has less like the review but
él tenga menos like el review sino de
that one minister referring to another
que un ministro refiriéndose a otro
has less line less repercussion than
tenga menos line menos repercusión que
the blond believed that he was crying for
el rubio creía que estaba llorando por
himself it
el mismo
is not for nothing that he has put the turn and
no es por nada que ha puesto el turn y
with the captures and all
con las capturas y todos
or rather with the  screenshots and all that, there's
o sea con las capturas y todo eso
also talk about 10,600, the
también se habla de 10.600 la
importance of which makes you reflect, what does
importancia de que te hace reflexionar
society care about? I mean,
que que le importa a la sociedad o sea
let's see, friends, friends, especially
vamos a ver amigos amigos en especial a
young people, but friends, friends, well, that's how it is
los jóvenes pero amigos amigos pues es
and surely my
que eso es así y seguramente a mi
lordship cares more about the videos that I
señoría le importe más los vídeos que yo
upload of arroz, son, and de la pantoja
suba del arroz hijito y de la pantoja
than what I put on any minister,
que lo que ponga en cualquier ministro
what logic is this? I
que lógica es esta
don't understand,
no entiendo
you
usted
boomer, fight against Alexa goes wrong,
boomer pelea contra alexa sale mal lo
whatever goes wrong is that I'm not an expert
que salga mal es que no soy un experto
in love,
en el amor
Alexa, I love you,
alexa te quiero
thank you for your skin
gracias por tu piel
[Music]
[Música]
is great, I will
es genial
always be here with you
siempre estaré aquí contigo
[Music]
[Música]
to those who are cut,
a las que se les cortan
maybe there is the ministry, spending the
a lo mejor está el ministerio pasarse el
goodbye, the wars, the mornings, there will be
adiós las guerras las mañanas
people, there will be people who have been
habrá gente habrá gente que se ha
offended by this because they believe that
ofendido por esto porque se cree que
this tweet from the blond is literally very
este tuit del rubio literalmente es muy
serious, there are
en serio
people in politics,
hay gente en política
thank you very much, I send you a huge hug,
muchísimas gracias te mando un abrazo
society cannot remain alive
la sociedad no puede permanecer vida en
around an Andalusian publication and
torno a un publicación andaluces y
hundreds stopped while the commission was
cientos paradas mientras fue la comisión
while society cannot remain
mientras la sociedad no puede permanecer
asleep or entertained around a
dormida ni entretenida en torno a un
colleague waiting for voices and  being
colega esperando voces y siendo chorrada
mental nonsense of games what the [ __ ] do you want
mental de juegos que [__] quieres que
people to watch to entertain themselves and more the
vea la gente para entretenerse y más los
kids play a video mica while
chavales juegan a un vídeo mica mientras
playing a video
juega un vídeo
[Music] look
[Música]
at me I mean
mírame
about the criticism I really don't
quiero decir de la crítica de verdad no
understand the complaint I mean it
entiendo la queja ósea
's worrying the kids in their
es preocupante a los chavales en su
free time start enjoying
tiempo libre se pongan a disfrutar de
weird content or rather literally me
contenido raro o sea el literal yo
when I want to disconnect and when I
cuando quiero desconectar y cuando
want to rest when I'm not
quiero descansar cuando no estoy
working and I start watching content
trabajando y me pongo a ver contenido
in most cases no what I'm
en la mayoría de ocasiones no lo que
looking for are things that are easy to digest
busco son cosas fáciles de digerir
easy things that entertain me to ximo
cositas fácil que me entretenga a ximo
come back whatever no
regrese lo que sea no
and if you really think that if I had
y si de verdad crees que si hubiese
put
puesto
a charitable soul that sums me up in favor
un alma caritativa que me resuma a favor
for patricia it's basically a minister
por patricia básicamente es un ministro
crying or a person a politician
llorando o una persona un político
government I don't know
gobierno no sé
crying because rubin has more
llorando porque el rubin tiene más
followers than them
seguidores que ellos
and is worried that society
y le preocupa que a la sociedad le
cares more about what I have done weird because
importe más eso que he hecho raro porque
literally also look at you how
literalmente además fíjate tú cómo son
things are that a minister
las cosas que nunca un ministro
is never very difficult to be a guarantor never say
es muy difícil ser avale nunca digas
never but very difficult will be the case
nunca pero muy difícil será el caso
will never have more followers than a
nunca va a tener más seguidores que un
youtube I mean because youtube you know there will
youtube o sea porque youtube lo sabes
be times in  those that do because it's
habrá ocasiones en las que sí porque es
YouTube, the least known inferior or
el youtube el inferior menos conocido o
most popular minister or whatever, no, or
ministro más popular o lo que sea no o
for example
por ejemplo
a very popular politician, what do I tell you,
un político muy popular que te digo yo
cheat, no, Donald Trump has many
trampa no donald trump tiene muchos
followers,
seguidores
Obama, people are known worldwide,
obama la gente mundialmente conocido
but for example, a minister or a
pero por ejemplo un ministro o un
politician from Spain is known and will
político de españa es conocido y le va a
only follow him in Spain, it's very
seguir solamente este en españa muy
difficult for someone
difícil es que le interese ver a alguien
who likes politics and who follows
que le guste la política y que siga a
people from other countries to be interested, but
gente de otros países pero un youtube lo
everyone sees YouTube.
ve todo el mundo
I have followers in Latin America and
yo tengo seguidores en latinoamérica y
in the United States.
en estados unidos
We
nosotros
ask to frame,
pido enmarcar
the people who spend this with people for
la gente que pasa esto con gente para
politicians or very extensive people,
políticos o gente muy extensa
just
solo
different,
distinto
that is mixing speed with
que está mezclando la velocidad con el
bacon, as we say many times, what does what
tocino como decimos muchas veces no que
kids see
tiene que ver lo que vean los chavales
on the internet have to do with what interests them in
en internet con lo que le interese en la
politics, goodbye, do you see that
política adiós hacer usted ve que la
people,
gente
so that you make people
para así hacer usted de que la gente se
interested in you, but I don't even
interese por ustedes pero yo ni siquiera
know,
sé
Minister of Inclusion, Social Security,
ministro de inclusión seguridad social
Immigration of the government and Alfonso Muñoz,
inmigración del gobierno y alfonso muñoz
this would be like its carrier, no, because
este sería como su portador no porque
I am seeing the same thing, no inclusion,
estoy viendo desde lo mismo no inclusión
social security and migrations, I
seguridad social y migraciones
imagine  If it's from the government of the
imagino que si es del gobierno del
Spanish government of the PSOE, we can't,
gobierno de españa del psoe no podemos
we have
tenemos
how I am, I
cómo
jump, guys, fix everything, I'm going to
soy salto tíos fijar todo lo voy a
fire you,
despedir
this can't continue like this, really, I
esto no puede seguir así de verdad tanto
got so involved, this isn't the [ __ ] of
me metí yo esto no es la [__] de
channels, you or the channel, it's disgusting,
canales a ti o la del canal es asqueroso
what's out there, plus salsa
que hay por ahí plus salsa
of the day
del día
[Music]
[Música]